Guide to the School of Medicine, Yale University, Matriculation Books, Registers, and Grade Books
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
School of Medicine, Yale University, matriculation books, registers, and grade books
1835-1967
RU 455
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
2.25
The records consist of examination and matriculation grade books and registers of students in the Medical Institution of Yale College (1835-1849) and the Yale Medical School.
Yale University. School of Medicine
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 27-F (YRG 27-F), Student records of the Yale School of Medicine.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is partially restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of examination and matriculation grade books and registers of students in the Medical Institution of Yale College (1835-1849) and the Yale Medical School.
College students; Medical students; Grade books; Yale College (1718-1887). Medical Institution; Yale University -- Examinations; Yale University -- Students; Yale University. School of Medicine
- School of Medicine Grades, 1877-1924; Accession 1981-A-024
  - Grades on Examinations, 1877-1902 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Grades on Examinations, 1901-1924 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Grades on Matriculation Examinations, 1902-1908 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- School of Medicine Registers, 1835-1965; Accession 1981-A-020
  - Record of the members of the Medical Institution of Yale Collge [see also YRG 37-A], 1835-1849 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Register, 1887-1904 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Register, 1904-1920 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Register, 1921-1929 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Register, 1930-1937 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Register, 1933-1936 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Register, 1938-1944 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Register, 1944-1951 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Register, 1951-1957 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Register, 1957-1965 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- School of Medicine Matriculation Books, 1875-1967; Accession 1981-A-019
  - Matriculation Book, 1875-1887 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Matriculation Book, 1887-1925 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Matriculation Book, 1925-1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)